chicagoreader.com 2017-06-26

# Chicago Reader | About | PrivacyPolicy

## This Privacy Policy applies to our sites and apps

We are Chicago Reader, a publication of Sun-Times Media, LLC. This Policy describes how we treat personal information. This includes our websites and our mobile apps.

To download a full copy of this Privacy Policy, click here.

## We collect information from and about you.

**Contact information.** For example, we might collect your name and street address. We might also collect your phone number or email.

**Payment information.** For example, we collect your credit card number when you access parts of our sites (e.g., Reader Real Deal).

**Information you submit or post.** We collect the information you post in a public space on our websites.

**Demographic information.** We may collect information about your interests or hobbies. We might collect this as part of a survey, for example.

**Other information.** If you use our websites, we may collect information about the browser you're using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. If you use our mobile app, we may collect your GPS location. We might look at how often you use the app and where you downloaded it. We collect this information using tracking tools.

↑ Back to top

## We collect information in different ways.

**We collect information directly from you.** For example, if you register for our newsletter. We also collect information if you post a comment or make a request. We may publish your name if you send a letter to the editor.

**We collect information from you passively.** We use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. We also collect information from our mobile apps.

**We get information about you from third parties.** For example, our business partners may give us information about you.

↑ Back to top

## We use information as disclosed and described here.

**We use information to respond to your requests or questions.** For example, we might use your information to register you for a contest. We may use your friend's email address if you send them information from our sites.

**We use information to improve our products and services.** We might use your information to customize your experience with us.

**We use information to look at site trends and customer interests.** We may use your information to make our websites and products better. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.

**We use information for security purposes.** We may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our websites.

**We use information for marketing purposes.** For example, we might send you information about special promotions or offers. We might tell you about new features or products. These might be our own offers or products, or third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. We may use push notifications on our mobile apps. To manage this, read the choices section below.

**We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship.** We may contact you about your account. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.

**We use information to talk to parents or guardians to get permission.** We may use contact information to get permission from parents for children who want to use our sites.

**We use information as otherwise permitted by law.** For example, we may use your IP address for identification purposes in cooperation with internet service providers or law enforcement agencies.

↑ Back to top

## We may share information with third parties.

**We will share information within the Sun-Times Media, LLC. family of companies.**

**We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.** For example, we share information with vendors who send emails for us or fulfill your purchases.

**We will share information with our business partners.** For example, we might share information with a business partner who runs a sweepstakes for us. These partners may send you information about events and products by mail or email. To control this, read the choices section below.

**We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.** For example, we will share information at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, or to verify or enforce compliance with our internal policies and applicable laws. We will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. Or, we might also share information when we are investigating potential fraud. This might include fraud we think has happened during a sweepstakes or promotion. We may share your information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our liability or to protect or enforce the rights, interests or safety of our products and services, our users or others.

**We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.** For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

**We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.**

↑ Back to top

## You have certain choices about our marketing and tracking tools.

**You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails.** To stop receiving our promotional emails, follow the instructions in any promotional message you get from us. You may still receive transactional messages.

**You can control tools on your mobile devices.** For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your mobile device. Each push notification has an "unsubscribe" link.

↑ Back to top

## Our sites and children.

Our sites and apps are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can [email](mailto:privacy@wrapports.com) us. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries "COPPA Information Request."

↑ Back to top

## We use standard security measures.

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords.

We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

↑ Back to top

## We store information in the United States.

If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. Our sites are subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country.

↑ Back to top

## We may link to other sites or have third party services on our sites we don't control.

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This includes sites that include our logo because we partner with that company. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website. That website sets its own cookies, collects data and /or has its own privacy practices. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party sites.

Our sites may also serve third party ads or content that contains the third party's own cookies or tracking technologies. We do not control the use of those technologies.

↑ Back to top

## Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.

If you have any questions about this Policy or other privacy concerns, please [email](mailto:privacy@wrapports.com) us.

You can also write to us or call at:

Chicago Reader  
350 N. Orleans Street, 10-S  
Chicago, IL 60654  
Attention: Legal - Privacy  
Phone:312-321-3000

↑ Back to top

## We may update this Policy.

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our websites. Please check our sites periodically for updates.

© 2013 Sun-Times Media, LLC. All rights reserved.
